buddybackup.com 2019-06-24

# BuddyBackup: Safe, Free and Secure Data Backup

We take your privacy and the protection of your personal data seriously. We will only store, process and disclose your personal data in accordance with the law. 

##  Privacy when using the BuddyBackup software 

(In this context “user” is anyone using the BuddyBackup software and “buddy” is a user whom you have manually given permission to backup to you). 

###  Information Collected by the Software 

When you setup your BuddyBackup account we will ask for your e-mail address. This will only be used by us to send you important account information (e.g. password reminders) and information about the BuddyBackup software. 

The password you choose during setup is optionally saved securely on our server. This is purely to allow you to request a password reminder if you forget your password. You can choose to remove your password from our server at any time (see here). In this case please be aware if you forget your password you will not be able to restore your backups. You can also choose to not provide your password during setup; in this case we will never know your password. 

We do not store your backups or details about your files on our servers. 

We will NEVER access your backups stored on your buddies’ computers, or access details about your files. If you choose to not store your password on our server as described above, we CANNOT access your backups as in this case you hold the only copy of your password. 

The BuddyBackup software will capture your public and private (local) IP addresses in order to help you connect with your buddies. 

We will keep a record of your last logon time and a figure of the total amount of data you have backed up (but not details about filenames, files sizes or numbers of files). This is purely for administrative purposes, and to help us improve the BuddyBackup service. 

We use a Crash Report Tool to collect (with your permission) information about crashes or software errors in BuddyBackup. These reports may contain other personal information about you or your files. You will be asked for permission by the software before it sends this report, and you can decline to send it. Received reports will be stored securely and used purely for improving the software. 

###  How your information is stored 

All the information we collect is stored securely on our server using firewalls, and is protected by strong passwords. 

Your backups are encrypted before sending to your buddies/USB drive. No other BuddyBackup user can read your files, not even your buddies. If you choose a [strong password](http://www.microsoft.com/protect/fraud/passwords/create.aspx) and you keep your password secret, your files/backups will be very secure. 

###  Use of information collected by the software 

We will only pass personal data captured by the BuddyBackup software to third parties where required to do so by law, where it is necessary to carry out or enforce a contract between us (and in that case subject to appropriate safeguards) or where we have your explicit permission to do so, with the following exception: 

  * Your IP addresses and e-mail address are provided to your named buddies. This information is sent securely using SSL. 

###  More Information 

The Data Controller for data collected by the BuddyBackup software is BuddyBackup Limited, and any questions relating to data protection or privacy should be addressed to The Data Protection Officer. Our contact details are BuddyBackup Ltd, Arxcis House, Unit 6, 9 Park Hill London, United Kingdom, SW4 9NS. 

##  Privacy when using the BuddyBackup website 

If you email us, or respond to any of the response forms on this site, we will receive the information you send us, and we will handle this as set out below. 

Our host may capture your IP address, but we obtain this material simply as a statistical report of web access (the IP address may be linked with a reverse DNS search which may or may not indicate the origin of the browsing).We cannot be responsible for the content or privacy policy on sites run by others, including those to whom we have linked, and you should satisfy yourself of those sites' privacy policy prior to revealing any personal information. You should also note that jurisdictions outside the European Union (including the United States) may not have data protection laws which are regarded as adequate by the European Commission. 

This site may use Cookies for the purposes of identifying users when logging in. 

The Data Controller for data on this site is BuddyBackup Limited, and any questions relating to data protection or privacy should be addressed to The Data Protection Officer. Our contact details are BuddyBackup Ltd, Arxcis House, Unit 6, 9 Park Hill London, United Kingdom, SW4 9NS. 

If you email us or respond to any of the response forms or registration pages in this web site, we will store your information to assist with future correspondence and provide services as set out below, but we will not give anyone else access to the information you give us (unless we are required to do so by law) or as set out below. If you wish us to delete or amend any information, please contact the Data Protection Officer. If you provide us with details of a third party, or if you use someone else's email address to respond to this web site, you must inform us, otherwise we will assume that we are receiving the personal data directly from you and that you have the appropriate permission to transfer it to us. 

We will use your personal data to (a) provide and administer services which we have agreed to provide to you, including providing upgrades, support, maintenance and troubleshooting (whether live or demo or demo versions); (b) administer accounts and collection of money for those services; (c) enforce the terms of any contract between you and us; (d) provide training to our staff and contractors; (e) provide you with information of further goods and services which we believe you may be interested in (please inform us using the contact details set out here if you do not want us to use your personal data for this purpose); (f) improve and develop our customer service, responsiveness, products and services. 

We will only pass personal data to third parties where required to do so by law, where it is necessary to carry out or enforce a contract between us (and in that case subject to appropriate safeguards) or where we have your explicit permission to do so. 

##  Website Terms 

BuddyBackup Limited is a limited company. Correspondence in the UK may be addressed to BuddyBackup Ltd, Arxcis House, 9 Park Hill, London, SW4 9NS 

BuddyBackup is a trademark of BuddyBackup Limited. 

The contents of this web site are copyright © 2005-10 BuddyBackup Limited. All rights reserved. You may copy anything in this web-site only to the extent that (1) to do so is necessary for browsing the web-site or (2) you are storing it in a cache. You may not include anything in this web site in another web site or copy it or print it (except for your internal purposes) without our explicit written permission (contact us for permission). Please do not link to any page other than the home page: we hold the copyright in the URLs of all pages and objects on this web site and any licence granted to you to browse this site does not (in the absence of our explicit written permission) extend to copying those URLs for deep linking or related purposes. 

This site contains links to external sites for your convenience only. We do not endorse, or recommend those links or the contents of their destinations, and links (and the content of their destinations) may change from time to time without our (or your) knowledge. 

Once you have left our site, these terms no longer apply.
